<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Activity Coding Challenge</string>
    <string name="first_text">Text One</string>
    <string name="second_text">Text Two</string>
    <string name="third_text">Text Three</string>
    <string name="paragraph1">India (Hindi: Bhārat), officially the Republic of India (Hindi: Bhārat Gaṇarājya),[23] is a country in South Asia.
        It is the second-most populous country, the seventh-largest country by land area, and the most populous democracy in the world.
        Bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast,
        it shares land borders with Pakistan to the west;[f] China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the north; and Bangladesh and Myanmar to the east. In the Indian Ocean,
        India is in the vicinity of Sri Lanka and the Maldives; its Andaman and Nicobar Islands share a maritime border with Thailand and Indonesia. </string>
<string name="paragraph2">Nepal (English: /nɪˈpɔːl/;[19] Nepali: नेपाल [nepal]), officially the Federal Democratic Republic of Nepal,
    [20] is a sovereign country in South Asia. It is mainly in the Himalayas, but also includes parts of the Indo-Gangetic Plain.
    It is the 49th largest country by population and 93rd largest country by area. It is landlocked and borders Tibet in the north and
    India in the south, east and west, while Bangladesh is located only 27 km (17 mi) from its southeastern tip and Bhutan is separated from
    it by the Indian state of Sikkim. Nepal has a diverse geography, including fertile plains, subalpine forested hills, and eight of the world\'s
    ten tallest mountains, including Mount Everest, the highest point on Earth.
    Kathmandu is the capital and the largest city. Nepal is a multiethnic country, with Nepali as the official language.
    </string>
    <string name="paragraph3">
       China, officially the People\'s Republic of China (PRC), is a country in East Asia. It is the world\'s
        most populous country, with a population of around 1.4 billion.[8] Covering approximately 9.6 million square kilometers
        (3.7 million mi2), it is the world\'s third or fourth-largest country by area.[l] As a one-party state led by the Chinese Communist Party (CCP),
        the country is officially divided into 23 provinces,[m][18] five autonomous regions,
        four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
    </string>
    <string name="button_key">TextView</string>
    <string name="heading1">INDIA</string>
    <string name="heading2">NEPAL</string>
    <string name="heading3">CHINA</string>
</resources>